Antonio Guilherme Lima Nunes

Avenida Mendes da Rocha, 1093 | Jardim Brasil | São Paulo | Brazil CEP 02227-001 E-mail: tgee565@gmail.com Brazilian, Married, 32 Years old (11) 98492-3704

Objective

Quality Assurance Engineer

Summary

Quality Assurance Engineer since 2015, experienced in testing across Mobile, Web, and Back-End platforms. Proficient in both soft and hard skills, including test planning, test writing, test execution, and bug reporting. Extensive experience in automation testing for Mobile (Native and Hybrid), Front-End(Angular, Node, VueJS), and Back-End(Restful), using leading frameworks and languages. Strong background in continuous integration, software versioning tools, and agile methodologies (Scrum, Kanban, Lean, XP, and Agile Testing). Experienced in working in international teams using English as the main language for communication.

Technical Skills

Development Languages:

- Java 9 Years
- Ruby 8 Years
- JavaScript 7 Years
- TypeScript 2 Years
- Kotlin 3 Years
- Swift 3 Years
- Groovy 7 Years

Testing Expertise:

- Angular Testing 10 Years
- SQL 9 Years
- Cucumber Framework 9 Years

Domain Frameworks:

- Mobile: Appium (Android/iOS), Espresso, XCUITest, Katalon Studio
- Back-End: Postman, HTTParty, REST Assured, various databases
- Front-End: Cypress, Selenium WebDriver, Capybara, SitePrism

Versioning & CI/CD:

- Git, Jira, GitHub, GitLab, Bitbucket
- Jenkins CI, BitRise, GitHub Actions, Docker, BrowserStack

Languages

Portuguese: NativeEnglish: Fluent

Educational Background

- Analysis and Development of Systems Uninove Universidade Nove De Julho -Graduated in 06/2017
- Selenium Caelum
- Appium Caelum
- MySQL Cognizant
- Agile Methodologies K21
- HTTParty Udemy
- Continuous Integration Udemy
- Scrum Foundations Professional Certificate

Professional Experience

Questrade Canada (2023/01 - Current)

Product Area: Investments

Quality Assurance Engineer Specialist

- Writing, running, and developing tests, test plans, test cases, BDD, and automated tests using Cypress and Rest Assured.
- Working in a Canadian team using the best agile methodologies.

Thoughtworks USA (2022/01 - 2023/01)

Product Area: Technology

Quality Assurance Engineer Specialist

- Writing and developing test plans, test cases, BDDs, and automated tests using Cypress, Rest Assured, and Appium.
- Working inside an international team using best agile practices.

DASA (2021/04 - 2022/01)

Product Area: Laboratory Medicine Quality Assurance Engineer Specialist

• Implemented functional E2E automated tests for a high-performance API using Rest Assured.

PagSeguro (2019/08 – 2021/04)

Product Area: Fintech

Quality Assurance Engineer SR / Quality Assurance Engineer Specialist

- Specialized in mobile testing using various techniques, tools, and CI/CD integrations.
- Worked on three key apps: PagBank, PagVendas, and Auditek.
- Led testing efforts for critical software releases: Design System, SmartPOS payment system, and SmartPOS X Payment System.

Fcamara (Buscapé) (2017/07 - 2019/07)

Product Area: Consultancy

Quality Assurance Engineer Analyst

• Conducted testing strategies and implementation for various projects.

Lyra Network (2016/06 – 2017/06)

Product Area: Payments

Quality Assurance Engineer JR

Quality assurance testing for payment processing systems.

Cognizant (2015/08 – 2016/08)

Product Area: Consultancy **Quality Assurance Intern**

Assisted in software testing, writing test cases, and debugging applications.

Social Media

- YouTube Channel (Quality Assurance): oqalizando
- LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/antonio-lima-qalizando/